{
    "id": "cf3516557220497c8240442042a5ddd7",
    "title": "Simple, Complex Vs. Compound",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Owing to his illness, he could not attend the meeting.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d67b2cae1ce04f3fa955941c3e6aa765"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor said that I had to quit smoking.",
            "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6062bfd2de9847628766d4029e6f243c"
        },
        {
            "question": "That carpet needs to be cleaned.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2a07cc1681144b88be62c5457630303d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you miss me when I am away?",
            "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e97735cd72584133aec17462697016ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "I miss living in the mountains.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e4fbda5bdf584907ba9e404e207c9a68"
        },
        {
            "question": "The missing girl was found at her auntâ€™s place.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "89c8988537a84140acbebd731b4997da"
        },
        {
            "question": "How they reached there is unknown.",
            "description": "A complex sentence has one main clause and one or more subordinate clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple sentence",
                "Complex sentence",
                "Compound sentence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "23cab9b0c38b4698b4bde4d55fa3f1cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "She opened the book and started making notes.",
            "description": "A compound sentence has two or more independent clauses of the same rank.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "714f56e2d40044838c0e53c352405928"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is neither intelligent nor efficient.",
            "description": "A compound sentence has two or more independent clauses of the same rank.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a10a31c802454abea81cd2c40c3f6219"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man told me to go away.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ac6dd449916a461caa7c38257c6b91b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He stopped to say Hi.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "03d72d98fc6f4fd1a8d5cbb328926b60"
        },
        {
            "question": "I must be losing weight.",
            "description": "A simple sentence has just one finite verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Simple",
                "Complex",
                "Compound"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f25d291ed514f8c97b10cb4ee48a4af"
        }
    ]
}